Guide to the Stuyvesant-Rutherfurd Papers 1647-1917 (bulk 1840-1917) MS 605
New-York Historical Society
- Other Series
  - Clippings (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Copy of Governor Stuyvesant's Commission (in Dutch) (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Copy of [Privy Council Minutes], 1761 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - [Sanskrit] Text on [Tree Bark], N.D. (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Samples of Monograms and Coats of Arms (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Seal of the Court of Probate of the State of New York (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Hair Clipping and Plant Clipping (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Fragments and Envelopes (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Blank Postcards (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Blank Legal Forms, Writing Paper, and Shipping Tags (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Printed Material -- Auction Catalogues -- Armor, 1893, 1895 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Printed Material -- Auction Catalogues -- Art, 1890, 1893 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Printed Material -- Astronomy, 1888, [1890], 1892, 1903 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Printed Material -- Business Brochures and Reports, 1831 - 1907 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Printed Material -- Charities, N.D., 1844, 1854, 1857, 1884 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Printed Material -- Constitution of St. Nicholas Society, 1835 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Genealogical Material, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Printed Genealogical Material, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Genealogical Material -- Notebook, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Artifacts (Box 27)
  - Photographs (Box 28)
  - Volume -- Tranquillity Farms Visitors' Book, 1891 - 1915, 1931 - 1933, 1947 (Volume Unknown container 668 for instance of Volume -- Tranquillity Farms Visitors' Book)
  - Volume -- Tranquillity Farms Payroll Book, 1904 - 1909 (Volume Unknown container 669 for instance of Volume -- Tranquillity Farms Payroll Book)
  - Volume -- Breeders' and Exhibitors' Kennel Record, 1883 (Volume Unknown container 670 for instance of Volume -- Breeders' and Exhibitors' Kennel Record)
  - Volume -- Mr. & Mrs. Stuyvesant & Children -- Cover Title "Forest & Stream & Rod & Gun", ca. 1860 - 1905 (Volume Unknown container 671 for instance of Volume -- Mr. & Mrs. Stuyvesant & Children -- Cover Title "Forest & Stream & Rod & Gun")